<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>security on Blogerinos</title>
    <link>/tags/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in security on Blogerinos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 11:01:50 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Security Commandments</title>
      <link>/2020/02/cloud-security-commandments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 11:01:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/02/cloud-security-commandments/</guid>
      <description>Preface The following list is my opinion on some of the top cloud controls that should be enabled within your environment. These can be security controls, processes, procedures or systems you create to manage and monitor your resources and users.
The List  Thou shalt use encryption everywhere. If its a checkbox, it gets turned on. Thou shalt not create public facing infrastructure without authorization or approval Thou shalt not blindly grant administration privileges to any principal Thou shalt follow the principle of least privilege when you are deploying policies or permissions Thou shalt not modify firewall rules to allow for all traffic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call the police - we got a bandit.</title>
      <link>/2020/01/bandit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 10:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/01/bandit/</guid>
      <description>The basics Today I would like to share with you some security lessons when using python. How we can use static linting to check our code for possible security flaws leveraging bandit. There will be some pretty obvious indicators of bad programming within this document, but only to demonstrate the power of the bandit. Not to highlight my inability to program. ☕️
First as always, we will create a virtual environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>